birkenstocks-store.com 2014-05-18

# Privacy Notice : Birkenstock Outlet

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information. We have instituted reasonable policies and security measures to protect the information you provide to us. When you register an account with our website, you give us your consent to process such submitted personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you businesses, consumers and the general public in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us, and to help you make informed decisions when using our website and all of our related services therein.

This privacy policy applies to all protected personal information collected, maintained or used by us.

**What Information We Collect:**

We collect personal data from visitors who register their information(e.g., name, gender, address, telephone number(s), email address, etc.) to create an account.

**How We Use Information You Provide:**

If you give us your personal information, then with your consent, we will use this information to keep you informed of our special events or promotions, and/or to process any orders you may place. Otherwise, we may use the information you provide to us only to review our performance and to improve our services to you, or to communicate with you about your order.

**Do We Share Your Information With Others:**

We will never sell, rent or disclose our clients' names, addresses, email addresses or other personal information to any entity. Unless we are required to do so by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding.
